From underdog to unstoppable.
Stephen Curry: Underrated is a documentary film directed by Peter Nicks.
The remarkable coming-of-age story of Stephen Curry—one of the most influential, dynamic, and unexpected players
in basketball history—and his rise from an undersized college player to a four-time NBA champion.
Self, played by Stephen Curry.
Self, played by Reggie Miller.
Self, played by Kevin Durant.
Self, played by Ayesha Curry.
Self, played by Draymond Green.
Self, played by Dell Curry.
Stephen Curry: Underrated is a 2023 American sports
documentary film about basketball player Stephen Curry.
The film was directed by Peter Nicks, and it premiered at the 2023 Sundance Film
Festival before being released in theaters and on Apple TV+ on July 21, 2023.
The film explores themes of biography, basketball,
historical figure, profile, sports documentary.